《黑镜》
《生死搏击》
(年岁酒吧)
就你自己吗
You here by yourself?
暂时是
So far.
真可惜  你这么漂亮
It's a shame. A pretty girl like you.
好吧
OK,
真俗
corny.
要不我请你喝一杯  作为弥补
Maybe I can make up for it by buying you a drink?
好啊
Sure.
- 酒保  - 来了
- Bartender. - Yeah?
来一杯巴克鸡尾酒  还有伏特加边车
Let me get a Buck and a vodka sidecar.
你为什么觉得我想喝伏特加边车
What makes you think I want a vodka sidecar?
也许我知道你喜欢什么
Maybe I know what you like.
你们在这呢
There they are.
来得正好
Right on time.
- 你好啊  卡尔  - 你好  这是黛西
- Hey, Karl. - Hey, what up, girl? This is Daisy.
黛西  这是丹尼和西奥
Daisy, this is Danny and Theo.
你好
Hey, lady.
他们就是我跟你说过的室友
This is my roommates I was telling you about.
他们谈恋爱
The ones who hooked up
纯粹是为了霸占最大的那间卧室
just so they can get the biggest room in the apartment.
没错
Very true.
- 我请你们喝一杯  - 没错
- Let me get you all a drink. - You're right.
你们赶紧去跳舞
Get your asses on the dance floor.
快去吧
Come on, girl.
好吧
Okay.
那一出"吧台偶遇"的戏码
That little role-play act, the stranger thing at the bar?
让我燥起来了
Got me hot as fuck.
我可得记住了  我家宝贝喜欢角色扮演
Mental note to self, my baby's into role-play.
这是属于你的声音
The sound is yours...
说对了
You know it.
当你和一屋子人一起劲歌劲舞
What do you do when you dance in a club
你会怎么做
and the place is packed and jamming?
第一回合  开始
Round one. Fight.
来得正好
You're just in time.
哥们我明天还得上班呢
Man, I gotta work tomorrow.
上什么班
Fuck your work.
新游戏
New game.
不不不不
No. No, no, no.
不
No!
该死
Fuck.
- 罗克赛胜利  - 好了  哥们
- Roxette wins. - All right, man.
- 再来一盘  - 不行  太晚了
- OK, one more. - No, man. It's too late.
就这么定了
Decision made.
该死
Shit.
看哪  你又挑了罗克赛
Look, he picks Roxette again.
你用兰斯也用了20多盘了
But you've been Lance for 20 bouts straight.
- 得了吧你  - 少废话了
- Come on. - I know you not bitching.
- 挑哪个战场  熊猫山吗  - 不去
- Where we going, Panda Mountain? - Mountain Sucks.
- 水晶滩  - 去古庙吧
- Crystal Beach? - Let's go for the Temple.
- 开始了  - 神秘古庙
- Here we go. - Secret Temple.
准备好被兰斯揍得半死吧
Get ready to get your ass kicked, Lance style.
是吗  罗克赛能把你的头操掉
Yeah? Roxette's gonna fuck your head off.
- 根本就说不通  - 把头操掉
- That don't even make sense. - Fuck your head off.
那是什么意思
What does that mean?
第一回合  开始
Round one. Fight.
快啊  快啊
Come on. Come on.
好了  起来  快点  加油  加把劲啊
All right, get up, come on. Come on. Come on.
不
No.
别闹了你
Get out of here.
- 喜欢吗  怎么样  - 处决
- You like? What now? - Negative.
- 加油啊  哥们  - 你完了
- Come on, man. - That's done.
KO  完美胜利
K.O. Perfect.
你们把我吵醒了
You woke me up.
太吵了
Too damn loud.
- 想抽点吗  - 宝贝
- You want some of this? - Baby.
"宝贝"
"Baby."
- 把那玩意关小点声  - 宝贝
- Quiet that shit down. - Baby.
宝贝  宝贝  宝贝
Baby! Baby! Baby!
(11年后)
寿星
Birthday boy!
Birthday boy.
祝贺你  你现在多少岁了
Congratulations. How old are you now?
38岁
38.
- 奔四十了  - 对
- Forty's a-coming. - Yeah.
离进棺材不远了
Soon be dead, huh?
是啊
Sure.
你见过西蒙吗
Have you met Simon?
- 应该没有  - 我们没见过面
- Don't think so. - I don't think we did, no, no.
好吧  西蒙喜欢车
OK. Simon's into bikes.
真酷
That's cool.
酷  真酷
Cool. That's cool.
麦克斯韦尔  不许踢人
Maxwell. We don't kick. No kicking.
看看他  抱歉失陪
Look at him. Sorry. I'm sorry.
- 你是喜欢摩托车还是自行车  - 自行车
- Do you like motorcycles or just bikes? - Just bikes.
酷
Cool.
- 抓到了  - 泰勒  快出去
- Tag! - Tyler, go on outside.
抱歉
Sorry!
- 抱歉  - 我来...
- Sorry. - Let me...
- 我来处理吧  - 洒到你身上了吗
- I'll get that. - Did he get it on you?
你...别担心
Yeah, you just... Don't worry.
卡尔
Karl.
- 西奥  - 我都多久没见过你了
- Hey, Theo. - I have not seen you in how long?
比久更久
However long, it feels longer.
黛西在停车吗
Is Daisy parking the car?
我和黛西已经不在一起了
Me and Daisy, no, we're not together anymore.
- 天啊  抱歉  - 所以...
- Oh, God, I'm sorry. - So...
不  没事的
No, no, no. It's... it's cool, really,
我们大概一年前就分手了
we broke up, like, a year ago.
我不知道  他...
No clue. He...
我不上脸书  所以
I'm not on Facebook, so...
这方面我真是什么都不懂
I can be a dumbass about these things.
真没关系的
No. Really, it's all good.
我们还是朋友  还是更好的朋友了
We're still friends. Better friends, actually.
处理得非常成熟
It's all very adult.
- 请进  快请进  - 好
- Well, come in, come in. - All right.
- 丹尼在后院  - 好
- Danny's out back. - OK.
不许打人也不许踢人  明白吗
We're not gonna punch, we're not gonna kick. OK?
- 抱歉  - 天啊
- I'm so sorry. - Oh, God.
好了  去玩吧  不许打架
OK, go play, no fighting.
该死  别啊
Goddamn it. Come on.
没什么比自家做的菜更好了
Can't beat a little home cooking.
- 哥们  - 你好吗
- Hey, man. - What's going on?
还改握手了
Handshake?
怕我传染你还是怎么着
What am I, like, infected or something?
去你的
Fuck you.
快过来  抱一个
Come on, get in here, man.
这样才像话嘛  放开点  别拘谨
Ah, that's better, let it out, buddy, let it out.
你还是个混蛋啊
You're still an asshole, I see.
生日快乐
Happy birthday.
你还开始用礼品包装袋了
When did you start using gift bags?
是商店送的
The store did that.
要打开看看吗
You gonna open it?
《生死搏击》
Striking Vipers.
X  《生死搏击X》
X. Striking Vipers X.
最新的一版  昨天才发售
Newest instalment. Came out just yesterday.
我刚好在商店
I was in the store,
看到了就...
I saw it and...
天啊
Oh, man.
想当年啊
This takes me back.
这里写  需要虚拟现实拓展组件
It says here you need one of those VR add-ons.
我没有那东西
I don't have one of those.
你有啊
Yes, you do.
不会吧
No.
不是吧  不行  伙计
No. No, come on, man.
不  今天是你生日  快收下  好吗
No. It's your birthday, just take the damn thing, would you?
真的  绝对让你爽翻天  我在店里试了
Seriously, you gonna flip the fuck out. I tried it out in the store.
他们让我看了五分钟小样
They demoed it for me. Five minutes
我脑子都炸开花了
blew my mind to confetti.
- 谢了  伙计  - 不客气
- Thanks, man. - It's all good.
那是你儿子吗
That your one?
不  那是麦克斯韦尔
No, that's Maxwell.
麦克斯韦尔  伙计们
Maxwell. Guys, guys.
泰勒在学校的小伙伴
Tyler's friend from school.
要来瓶啤酒吗  伙计
You want a beer, man?
他终于拯救了我  太好了
Finally he saves me. Yes.
谢了
Thank you.
妈妈  我一直在跟凯蒂玩
Mommy, Mommy, Mommy, I've been playing with Katie.
西奥  我们要用塑料杯子吗
Theo, are we using the plastic cups?
西奥看起来不错
Theo's looking good.
很高兴看到你俩至少还有一人在健身
Good to see at least one of you still has a gym membership.
是吗
Oh, really?
说真的  伙计
Seriously, man.
你现在走路就像个科学怪人似的
You're walking around like a fucking Frankenstein movie.
我膝盖坏掉后  一直没法健身  好吗
Look, since my knee went, I haven't been able to work out, all right?
我不是想找借口  我只是...
I'm not using that as an excuse. I'm just...
不  当然不是
No, no, no, of course not.
去你的  好吗
Fuck you, all right?
我能顺其自然了  我已经有妻有子了
I can afford to let things slide. I'm settled.
感谢上帝我不用再出去约会
I thank God I don't have to be out there on the dating scene.
随时等着被人挑什么的
Always on sale. Fucking bullshit.
那就像是第二份工作
It is like a second job.
还得跟紧那些年轻人的节奏
Gotta keep up with those younger dudes.
你每天得做一千个仰卧起坐吧
You gotta do a thousand crunches a day?
就每天早上做50个
Only 50 each morning.
早上50个
Fifty in the morning?
你会刮蛋上的毛吗
You wax your ballsack?
那些年轻人肯定会
I'm sure as shit those young dudes do.
你还真刮...太恶心了
You wax your ball... You nasty.
刮得像个闪闪发光的八号球
Till it's gleaming like an eight ball.
就为了保持撩妹的竞争力
Just to stay in the game.
- 我真是同情你  - 嗯  好吧
- I pity you, really. - Yeah. Well...
想知道我离开这里之后会去哪吗
You wanna know where I'm going after I leave here?
去刮屄和屁眼之间的毛吗
Shit, getting your taint waxed too?
去见玛丽耶拉
Meeting Mariella.
玛丽耶拉
Mariella.
她是做伴唱的
She does backing vocals.
给谁伴唱  学校乐团吗
What, for the school band?
她多大了
How old is she?
Twenty-nine.
不  28  看  这还是她
No, 28. See. Here she is again.
对
Yeah.
要给全班同学看看吗
You wanna share that with the class?
- 真是个幸运的男人  - 没错
- You lucky man. - I am, me.
你那是干什么
What are you doing?
你搞什么
泰勒睡了吗
Tyler asleep?
我又读了一遍那本马卡鲁的破书
Had to read that damn Macaroo book again
他才让我熄了灯
before he'd let me put out the light.
"马卡鲁发现了一只鞋..."
"Macaroo found a shoe..."
"把它放进了一棵树里"
"And put it in a tree."
马卡鲁一点都不尊重环境
Macaroo's got no respect for his environment,
我就这么一说
that's all I'm saying.
- 我来吧  - 没事的
- I can do that. - No, I'm fine.
今天是你生日  来吧
It's your birthday, come on.
谢谢
Thank you.
好了
Ok.
对了  你该告诉我卡尔和黛西分手了
You know, you should've told me that Karl and Daisy broke up.
- 他有说是谁提出来的吗  - 我没问
- Did he say who broke up with who? - I didn't ask.
我总说那俩人不会有什么好结果
I always said that those two were not good news together.
我好久没见着他了
So long since I saw him last.
上次见面还是去年生日吧
Had to be last year's birthday, I think.
有一整年没见了吧
In the flesh, a whole year?
他和他手机上的那个妹子  是认真的吗
Him and the girl on his phone, is that serious?
我没问
I didn't ask.
男人都不善于聊天
Guys suck at talking.
你俩认识多久了
How long have you two known each other?
这种场合根本没机会聊这些事  是吧
You don't actually get to talk at these things, though, do you?
也就只能闲聊
I mean, beyond surface bullshit.
再就是家长八卦  现在净说这个了
Or parent talk. There's a lot of that these days.
你们应该多一起玩玩
Y'all should hang out more.
你也知道的  工作忙
Yeah, well, you know, work.
我们是父母了
And we're parents.
他在城里做唱片  我们住在郊区
He's downtown with the label and we're out here.
我们应该请他来吃晚餐
We should have him over for dinner.
你可以做你拿手的辣椒
You could make your chili.
好啊
Sure.
危险餐具警告
Flatware hazard warning.
你得把刀刃朝下
You gotta put the knives in sharp edge down.
我知道
I know.
你看那人的罗德曼造型
Check out the Rodman look on this guy.
你好吗
How are you?
罗德曼
Rodman?
丹尼斯·罗德曼
Dennis Rodman.
- 他以前是个球员  对吗  - 对
- He used to be a ball player, right? - Right.
你是说发型
The hair.
明白了
Got it.
手机软件上说我们需要在一小时内完成
The app says we need to do it within the hour.
现在是受孕高峰期
It's peak fertility.
我有点累了  但我觉得我们应该试试
I'm kind of beat but I guess that we should.
你不想吗
You not into it?
我刚吃太饱了  不知道能不能行
I just ate so much, I don't know if I can.
最好还是留着下次吧
It's best to save it up, though, right?
介意我先睡了吗
Mind if I go to sleep?
睡吧
No.
我爱你  宝贝
I love you, baby.
我也爱你
Love you, too.
靠
Shit.
(卡尔邀请你玩《生死搏击X》)
伙计
Hey, man.
还没睡呢  想打盘游戏吗
Hey, you still awake? You wanna game?
今晚就不了  我在...
Maybe not tonight. I was...
别这样  你在玩什么
Come on, what are you playing?
我猜你在玩什么无聊的游戏
Something goddamn boring is what I'm guessing.
好吧  被你猜到了
All right, you got me.
那好  拿起我给你的体验盘
All right, so grab the experiencer disc I got you,
戴上  开始
put it on and jump in.
我说真的  好玩疯了
Seriously, man, it's insane.
能把你吓死
You're gonna freak.
你会吓到把盆骨拉穿
You're gonna shit your pelvis through your asshole.
- 好吧  怎么装  - 他们在店里装给我看了
- OK. What do I do? - All right, they showed me in the store.
- 把游戏芯片插进去  - 好了
- You put the game chip in. - Done.
现在拿出游戏盘装置  粘在头上
Now grab the disc doohickey and stick it upside your head.
- 左边还是右边  - 随便
- Left or right side? - Doesn't matter.
- 好了  - 好
- Done. - OK.
现在按住手柄上的同步按钮
Now hold down the sync button on the controller.
没反应
Nothing's happening.
还没选择战士
We haven't chosen our fighters yet.
那我选
So, I am...
罗克赛
Roxette.
好吧  那我的战士呢
OK, so where's my guy?
- 兰斯  - 靠  好啊  兰斯  开始吧
- Lance. - Damn. All right, Lance, let's go.
好  你可得做好准备
OK, you have to brace yourself.
"做好准备"  来吧
Brace myself. Come on.
- 准备好了吗  - 准备好了
- You ready? - Yeah, I'm ready.
三  二
Three, two...
一
one.
天啊
Oh, my God.
这太疯狂了
This is crazy.
- 怎么回事  - 喂  丹尼
- What the fuck...? - Yo, Danny.
我说了  你得做好准备
Said you gotta brace yourself.
卡尔
Karl?
很疯狂  对吧
Crazy shit, huh?
我觉得自己很壮
Like, I feel solid.
你以为你的胸肌算厉害吗  看看这对宝贝
You think your chest is impressive? Check this shit out.
- 这真是太...  - 我知道
- This is just... - I know, right?
你的膝盖怎么样
How's the knee?
很好
Pretty good.
在这里  你可以做很多在外面做不到的事
Man, in here, you can do so much shit you can't do out there.
杂技队长耍够了
OK, enough of the Captain Acrobat shit.
- 准备好开打了吗  - 准备好了
- You ready to fight? - I'm ready.
第一回合
Round one.
开始
Fight.
等一下
Hold on a minute.
我会疼吗
Is this going to hurt?
"本游戏模拟一切身体感觉"
"The game emulates all physical sensations."
到底会还是不会
Is that a yes or a no?
真的会疼
It does.
再见
Peace out.
我会打得你落花流水
I'm gonna fuck you up.
雷电拳
Thunder punch.
风车绝杀
Windmill wipe-out.
你就这点能耐吗
That the best you can do, man?
老天啊
Jesus Christ.
别担心  系统会重置  不会造成损伤
Don't worry, it resets. No harm done.
真变态
That's messed up.
第二回合
Round two.
- 等一下  该死  我生疏了  - 开始
- Hold on. Shit, I'm rusty. - Fight.
我都记不起他会什么招式了
I can't remember what moves this guy can do.
就像骑自行车一样
It's like riding a bike.
瞧  挡得好
See? Nice block.
谢了
Thanks.
极力重击
Hyperstrike!
这是双倍
That's double.
旋风腿
Tornado fury.
飞踢  飞踢  飞踢  飞踢
The leg, the leg, the leg, the leg.
不  不不  不行  不
No. No. No, no, no. No, no, no.
我怎么出去  我怎么才能出去
How do I get out of here? How do I get out of here?
退出游戏
Exit game.
(卡尔已退出游戏)
退...退出游戏
Exit... Exit game!
该死
Oh, shit.
我靠
Holy shit.
你好呀  小家伙怎么那么精神
Hello. Where did he come from?
我的出租车到了
That's my cab.
- 晚安  小家伙  - 晚安
- Good night, little man. - Good night.
- 帮我照顾好爸爸  好吗  - 好
- Take care of Daddy for me, OK? - OK.
我不确定几点回来
I'm not sure when I'll be back.
看堵不堵车吧
Depends on traffic, I guess.
玩得开心
Have fun, OK?
(溜冰俱乐部)
战略阵地
Battle stations.
"...他的鞋  把它放进了一棵树里"
"...his shoe and put it in a tree."
很好
Very good.
"亮亮的那面形成了一条滑梯
"The shiny side made a slide.
他快乐地滑了下去"
He slid down happily."
"他把树叶整理好"
"He fixed the leaves..."
游戏结束
Game over.
(卡尔已上线)
(卡尔邀请你玩《生死搏击X》)
你好啊
Hey, there.
我不能玩太久  我...
I can't play long, I...
没问题  我也是
Oh, sure, me too.
听着
Look...
上次玩的时候  我在派对上喝醉了
Last time we played, I was drunk, man, from the party.
我也是
Me, too.
好
Cool.
行
Ok.
能好好打一场真的很爽
Be good to have a serious game, you know?
好好打一场
Serious game.
开始吧
Here we go.
我要痛扁你了  混蛋
About to kick your ass, motherfucker.
是吗  你尽管试吧
Yeah? You're gonna try.
第一回合  开始
Round one. Fight.
- 拜托  别走  - 别闹  我要走了
- Come on, come on! Please, please! - Stop it! No! I'm going.
你能听到吗
Can you hear me?
是的  现在能听到了吗
Yes. Can you hear me now?
你是司机  对吧
You're the driver, right?
对  我在酒馆门口
Yeah, I'm outside of the Taphouse.
酒馆
Taphouse.
看来现在我们是同性恋了
So, guess that's us gay now.
开玩笑的
That's a joke.
感觉不像是同性恋
Don't feel like a gay thing.
- 怎么了  - 天啊
- What is it? - Jesus.
退出游戏
Exit game.
怎么了
What?
你怎么没在床上
You're supposed to be in bed.
我渴了
I'm thirsty.
你渴了
You're thirsty?
(卡尔  抱歉我退出了  泰勒醒了  踢了我的小腿)
- 你吃完了吗  - 吃完了
- You finished? - Yes.
吃完了  然后呢
Yes what?
- 吃完了  谢谢  - 去吧
- Yes, thank you. - Go ahead.
你好  妈妈
Hey, Mom.
你好  小伙子
Hey there, little man.
看来你需要喝一杯咖啡
Looks like you can use one of these.
感觉就像有条狗死在我脑袋里了
Feels like a dog died in my damn head.
你不应该喝酒的
You weren't supposed to drink.
我以为我的月经迟到了  我希望是
I figured my period was late. And I hoped it was.
结果我在外面时月经来了  所以
And then it came on while I was out, so.
我心想  去它的
I just said fuck it.
我很遗憾
I'm sorry.
还有下次
Next time.
亲鼻子上了
Nose kiss.
请在程序开始前冲洗碗盘
Please rinse dishes before program start.
第一回合  开始
Round one. Fight.
抱歉  宝贝
I'm sorry, baby.
我累了  好吗
I'm just tired, OK?
好吧  我看得出你有心事
OK, I know when you're thinking.
怎么了
What's up?
是什么感觉
How does it feel?
对你来说
I mean, like, for you,
在女人的身体里  然后
being in a woman's body while...
疯狂
Crazy.
太疯狂了
It's crazy.
我是说  不一样
I mean, it's different.
就是
Like...
肉体上的感觉
the physical feeling of it?
更加的
It's more sort of...
满足
satisfying.
我不知该怎么解释
I can't really explain it.
一种是吉他独奏
Like, one's a guitar solo,
另一种是整个管弦乐队
the other's a whole fucking orchestra.
但曲子基本上是一样的
But the tune's basically the same.
不过节拍不同
Different tempos, though.
嗯  这个比喻你用到家了
Yeah, I think you've run that analogy to the ground.
去你的
Fuck you.
我要你推我的脚
I'd like you to push my feet down.
听好了  先生
Listen here, mister.
听好了
Listen here.
(西奥  今晚找好保姆了  亲亲)
(为什么要找)
(结婚纪念日)
(谢谢你还记得)
该死
Shit.
(卡尔)
(今晚不行  结婚纪念日  抱歉  亲亲)
(今晚不行  结婚纪念日  抱歉)
我能不能...
Can I, uh...
是不是不该问
Should I not?
我只是想问能不能请你喝一杯
I was just gonna ask if I could buy you a drink.
- 抱歉  - 天啊
- I'm sorry. - Oh, God.
- 是的  - 我很抱歉
- Yeah. - I'm so sorry.
不用
Don't be.
不  说真的
No, seriously.
真不用
Seriously.
我不打扰你了
I'll leave you alone.
抱歉
Sorry.
- 还满意吗  - 很棒  谢谢你
- It's all good? - It was great, thank you.
甜点马上到
Your dessert's on the way.
味道不错
That was good.
你知道你有个习惯吗
You know the thing about you?
有时你会走开
Sometimes you just sort of go away.
- 什么意思  - 我是说你会走神
- What do you mean? - I mean, you shrivel away.
你进入自己的世界  把我留在外面
You go inside. Leave me on the outside.
你还在吗
Are you in there?
当然在
Of course I am.
好吧  那怎么回事
OK. So then, what's up?
没什么
Nothing.
我们几个星期没做了
We haven't done it in weeks.
我一直很累
I've been tired.
- 我们应该再试试的  - 我们在尝试
- We're meant to be trying again. - We are trying again.
不  你要是不操我  我就没法怀孕
No. Won't get pregnant if you don't fuck me,
- 丹尼  - 天啊
- Danny. - Jesus.
不是我不想做
It's not that I don't want to.
我说了我最近很累
I said I've been tired.
对不起
I'm sorry...
是出了什么事吗
but is something going on?
出了什么事
Something going on?
别重复我的话
That's what I said.
没什么事
Nothing is going on.
那怎么回事
Then what is it?
- 是我的原因吗  - 不是
- Is it me? - No.
- 你都不碰我了  - 西奥
- You don't touch me anymore. - Theo.
你都不亲我了
You don't even kiss me.
也没那些亲密的小动作了
There is none of the small stuff.
挤我的肩膀
Squeeze my shoulder.
在厨房经过我时摸我的背
A hand on my back as you pass me in the kitchen.
- 西奥  - 连这些都没了
- Theo. - Not even that.
你还想要我吗
Do you want me any more?
我永远想要你
I'll always want you.
不  你知道我的意思
No. You know what I mean, I mean, me.
我是说我的身体
This. This.
我知道我不如以前了
I know that I'm not what I was.
我的身体生了泰勒后发生了改变
My body is not what it was since Tyler.
别这么说
Don't say that.
你在跟别人约会了吗
Are you seeing someone?
没有
No.
那你为什么不要我了  你以前总想要我的
So why don't you want me? You always used to want me.
这很无聊  我懂的
It's boring, I get that.
家庭生活
Family life?
我也觉得无聊
Shit, I find it boring.
但我很忠诚
But I am loyal.
对我们的家庭忠诚  对你忠诚
I'm loyal to our family. I'm loyal to you.
要是我想  我也可以去放纵自己
God knows if I wanted, I could go out and do whatever.
你以为我没做出牺牲吗
You think I haven't made sacrifices?
我没拒绝过乐子吗
I haven't denied things for myself?
刚才有个人在酒吧跟我搭讪
A guy at the bar earlier tried hitting on me.
一半的我想由着他  找点刺激
Half of me wanted him to, just for some excitement,
找点激情
some fucking passion.
但你必须坚守住
But that is what you do.
这是配偶关系的一部分
It's part of being in a partnership,
你拒绝那些风流快活
you shut the door on all that shit.
你拒绝那些  因为你做了承诺
You shut it out because you have committed.
这正是承诺的意义
It's what a commitment is.
天啊  要是真有什么事  我就...
Oh, God. If something's going on, I just...
我就是想知道
I just want to know.
我该怎么办就会怎么办
I'll deal with it how I deal with it.
但我得知道
I just have to know.
根本没什么事
Nothing is going on.
我保证
I promise.
我发誓
I swear.
一份巧克力球冻
One chocolate bombe.
两柄勺子
And two spoons.
请享用
Enjoy.
就这样  很棒
That's it. That's good.
抱歉
Sorry.
我射不出了
I'm not gonna get there.
你又在担心工作的事了
You're worrying about your work again?
我想是的
I think so.
好吧
Ok.
介意我自己解决吗
Mind if I finish myself off?
(卡尔已上线)
(卡尔  你在哪)
- 等一下  不好意思  我要接一下  - 好的
- Hold on. Excuse me, I gotta take this. - Sure.
喂
Hello.
什么意思
What do you mean?
意思是我不能再这么下去了
It means I can't do it anymore.
这对西奥不公平
It's not fair to Theo.
但这不是出轨  那不是真的
But it's not cheating. It's not real.
就像是...黄片什么的
It's like... porn or something.
伙计  你知道那样做不对
Come on, man, you know it ain't right.
- 我必须考虑西奥  - 好吧  但是
- I gotta think of Theo. - OK. But...
我们不用完全断了
we don't have to completely cut it off.
能不能  每个月第一个周日之类的
What about, like, first Sunday of each month?
- 不  - 就偶尔
- No. - Just now and then.
卡尔  这必须停止  断干净
Karl, it has to stop. Clean break.
拜托  这明明很棒  明明很棒  你也清楚
Come on. This is good. This is good. You know it is.
我得挂了
Look, I gotta go.
- 对不起  - 丹尼
- I'm sorry. - Danny.
再见
Goodbye.
丹尼
Danny.
(七个月后)
我要过你了  准备好了吗  开始
I gotta get past you, you ready? Go.
好了
All right.
你赢了
You win.
他睡下了
And he is down.
马卡鲁又找到鞋子了
Macaroo found that shoe again, huh?
还放进了一棵树里
And put it in a tree.
生日快乐
Happy birthday.
抱歉没准备太多  我出不了门
Sorry it's not much. I couldn't get out.
我想要的就是这个
It's exactly what I wanted.
谢谢你
Thank you.
闻起来很棒
That smells good.
就是你喜欢的那种大碗红肉
It's the sort of red-meat caveman food you like.
没错  真是好一大份
Yeah. That's a hell of a serving size.
你的胃口又好了吗
You having your hunger pangs again?
今晚我们三个人吃
There's three of us eating tonight.
我就是这个意思
I know, that's what I said.
我是说三个大人
I mean, three adults.
我还邀请了卡尔
I invited Karl over.
惊喜吧
Surprise.
卡尔
Karl?
去年你说你几乎都见不到他了
Yeah, well, last year you said you hardly got to see him.
我们那次烧烤时  你也没和他说上话
You didn't get to speak to him at that barbecue we had.
于是我上周给他发了邮件
So I emailed him last week.
他怎么说的
And what did he say?
他说他很期待
He said he was looking forward to it.
说曹操曹操到
Speak of the devil.
天啊  你还记得我们当初在梅德利
Oh, my God, you remember that crazy dude
住在楼下的那个疯子吗
that lived downstairs when we were at Madeley?
以前我们放音乐时  他都会敲天花板
He used to bang on the ceiling when we played the music.
不过情有可原  我们的确很吵
He had a point, though, because we were loud.
宝贝  你记不记得有一次你拿来了摇头丸
Baby, you remember the time that you got that molly
非让我们都来一颗
and you insisted that we all take it?
我第二天还要上班呢
I had to go to work the next day.
天啊
Lord.
我们当时还年轻吧
We were young, I guess.
是啊
Well.
现在最疯狂也就是喝点轩尼诗和吃点甜点了
Hennessey and dessert is as crazy as it gets now.
说到甜点  快做好了
Speaking of dessert, it's almost ready.
你到底在干什么
What the fuck are you doing?
- 吃东西而已  - 我不是问这个
- Just eating. - That's not what I mean, OK?
你为什么来这里
Why the fuck did you come?
她叫我来的  你觉得我能说什么
She asked me to come. What do you want me to say?
- 找个借口  - 比如呢
- An excuse. - Such as what?
什么都行
Such as anything.
怎么  我是你前妻吗
What am I? Your ex-wife or something?
这太奇怪了  好吗
Look, it's too strange, OK?
真的太奇怪了
It's just too fucking strange.
我告诉你什么才叫奇怪
I'll tell you what's strange.
没什么能比得上  对不对
Nothing matches it, does it?
我也想找到替代品
I tried replacing it, man.
我试过
I tried.
我还上了电脑控制的人格角色
I tried fucking the computer-controlled characters.
- 太假了  - 闭嘴
- It's bullshit. - Shut up.
就像充气娃娃  没有任何性爱程序
It's like a rubber doll. Not programmed for any sex stuff.
他们就躺在那里
They just sort of lie there.
我也试过真玩家
I tried it with real players.
让其他人控制兰斯
Other folks controlling Lance.
其中有一个荷兰人
There was this one guy from Holland.
他还算凑合吧  只要我不去在意他的口音
He was kind of halfway OK as long as I didn't think about this accent.
但是我没感觉
But it didn't get me.
我没感觉  不像我们在那里时  我和你
It didn't get me, not like when we're in there. You and me.
够了
Stop it.
我什么都试过了
I tried everything.
我用过男性玩家  女性玩家
I've gone in there as guy players, girl players,
多位玩家NP  各种形式
multi-player gangbangs, you name it.
我甚至还上了谭德拉  那个北极熊角色
You know, I even fucked Tundra, the polar bear character.
我上了北极熊
I fucked a polar bear
可你还在我脑子里
and I still couldn't get you out of my mind.
我帮不了你
I can't help you.
你还想上罗克茜
You want to fuck Roxi again.
- 我不想  - 你想
- I don't. - You do.
- 别...  - 那是我这辈子最棒的性爱
- Just... - The best sex of my life.
你肯定也一样  简直是销魂蚀骨  你清楚得很
Best of yours too. Fucking transcendent. You know it was.
想想吧
Think about it.
想想她
Think about her.
罗克茜
Roxi.
抱着她
Holding her,
温暖的肌肤紧紧相贴
her warm skin against yours.
不要
Please.
她的屄又湿又紧
Her tight wet pussy.
- 我操  - 她午夜时会在里面等你
- Fuck, man. - She'll be in there at midnight.
你再进来一次吧  你肯定想的  最后一次
Just come on in one last time. You know you want to. One last time.
你们在干什么
What y'all doing?
- 瞎聊  - 瞎聊  对
- Bullshit. - Bullshit, yeah.
看起来很好吃
That looks good.
宝贝  盘子给我
Baby, your plate.
你做了提拉米苏吗
Is that your tiramisu?
没错
You know it.
全球闻名
World famous.
见到你很开心
Good to see you.
生日快乐
Happy birthday, man.
见到你很开心
It was good to see you.
我也是
Yeah, you, too.
天哪  快拥抱吧
Lord, hug each other.
你们男人可真尴尬
Guys can be so awkward.
午夜哦
Midnight.
- 再见  - 晚安
- Bye. - Good night.
我好爱这样
I love this.
我爱你
I love you.
不
No.
No!
我不知道我为什么那么说
I don't know where that came from.
这样下去会怎样
Where the fuck does this go?
你也感觉到了
You're feeling it, too.
说啊
Just say it.
说出来
Say it.
你到底想怎样
What the fuck do you want?
你以为能有什么结果
Where does this end?
谁说非得结束了
Who says it has to end?
- 你还记得年岁酒吧吗  - 丹尼
- You remember the Year Club? - Danny.
那家老酒吧  年岁酒吧
The old club, the Year.
我当然记得  怎么了
Of course I do, why?
后面的停车场  半小时后在那等我
Car lot out back. Meet me there in 30 minutes.
退出游戏
Exit game.
- 好吧  - 我们不是来打架的
- OK. - We're not gonna fight.
我们要亲嘴
We're gonna kiss.
亲嘴
Kiss?
就是  接吻
Like... kiss.
只有这样才行  我们必须得确认
It's the only way. We gotta know.
确认什么
Know...
如果有感觉
If there are fireworks,
那我们  就能成
then, OK, bam, it's an "us" thing, whatever.
至少我们心里有底了
At least we've got a foothold on it.
所以干脆就亲一个
So let's just fucking kiss.
好吧
Ok.
我说了好
I said OK.
让我酝酿一会儿
I'm working up to it.
- 要我主动吗  - 我怎么知道
- You want me to start? - I don't know.
也行
Yeah.
好吧
Ok.
准备好了吗
You ready?
赶紧亲吧  哥们
Just fucking kiss me, man.
没感觉
Nope.
什么都没有
Not a damn thing.
我也是  没感觉
No, me neither.
看来说清楚了
So that settles it.
你知道在游戏里是不一样的
You know it's different in the game.
不行
No.
你得忘记这些愚蠢的想法
You got to get that shit out of your head.
- 忘不掉了  哥们  - 不行
- It ain't coming out, man. - No.
- 已经深埋在脑子里了  - 去你妈的
- It's burrowed right in there. - No, fuck you.
就在这里  哥们
Burrowed right in there, man.
我知道  你也知道
I know it, you know it.
埋在你的脑子里了  是吗
It's buried in there, huh?
- 或许打你一顿你就忘了  - 别推我
- Maybe we can get rid of it like that. - Don't push me, man.
- 你是大男人吗  推你怎么着  - 别推我
- You a big man? What you gonna do? - Don't push me.
就推你了怎么着
What you gonna do?
好吧
Ok.
停
Stop.
别打了  别打了
Stop! Stop!
我丈夫在这
My husband's here.
- 他叫丹尼  丹尼尔·帕克  - 丹尼尔·帕克
- Danny, Daniel Parker. - Daniel Parker.
我知道你们两个晚餐时在吵架
I knew y'all were mad at each other over dinner.
你们到底在吵什么
So, what were you fighting about?
听见了吗
Hello?
妈了个逼的
Holy fuck!
跟我说话啊
Talk to me.
你们把孩子带进来
You guys, bring the kids in.
你们真会生孩子
You guys make great babies.
- 我家孩子丑得啊  - 什么
- Ours look like a mile of bad road. - What?
我要是个保姆就好了
I wish I was a baby-sitter.
生日快乐
Happy birthday.
明天早上还我
I want that back in the morning.
你也是
Ditto.
(丹尼已上线  生死搏击X)
- 准备好了吗  - 我准备好了
- You ready? - I'm ready.